[Music]
we're back in canada and it feels so
good
to uh rip this guy
around man i am having so much fun
driving around the jaguar again we're
living in a friend's place here for a
few months before we get settled
somewhere else we're just started a
productive grind here now guys i know uh
i talk a lot about doing
one focus at any given time and
the focus for the past six months was
traveling around exploring everything
like that now what we're gonna do is
we're really hitting the youtube scene
hard here thus this video i'm going to
teach you guys a lot of gems this is
similar logic to how i've been training
lately and i've been developing while
i've been traveling around i recently
posted something here i'll brought up
something that's basically uh what i
post on instagram here for my friends
and everything and i'm i'm challenging
people i'm saying hey post
uh some sort of challenge you've been
wanting to do and i'm gonna match you uh
like some sort of fitness challenge or
educational challenge something like
that if you guys have any suggestions
throw them in the comment section below
what have you been wanting to do
uh a challenge for personal growth and i
will maybe match you on that too because
i'm on a binge here guys and we're gonna
get a lot of done over the next few
months uh let's dive into a strategy and
check out the new place see you guys
[Music]
all right so we're on
some strategy here still shirtless i
don't wear clothes at home boys
take a look there you go but um what
we're doing here on uh we're mostly
trading more on the the the nasdaq we're
trading on the um
the bitcoin and then we've also been
doing the eu and gu that we used to do
and those are still going to be staying
kind of the same uh we're trying to take
more of a
uh on on the eu and gu trades we're
taking more of a uh wait for the sweep
and then follow back into the trend
based thing and as always what we want
to be doing
in our strategies is we want to be
developing the higher time frame bias
first of all so hopefully you guys can
kind of see the chart here fine i do
have the four screens now it is helping
me because i do watch a lot more stuff
now um and
we generally want to be following that
higher timeframe bias uh now the thing
that we really want to do is i do have a
video series called uh price action
based trend trading and this is quite
similar to that you guys will notice
there's a certain indicator on here
we're not always following these lines
but it's really good to draw the levels
and it's really good for drawing the
trends and i will reveal uh what this
indicator is it's still in the works
it's still being developed but once it's
done
i will give um my buddy a message and he
will um
give me a link that i can share with you
guys so whenever he's done with it i
know you're watching there uh send me a
message uh when we're ready and we'll
release it to everyone so that they can
they can get in on it it is it's cheap
uh but it's uh not free just so you guys
know um and i'm testing it out and it
really does help kind of the way that
we're trading here in terms of trend
based trading it's a good combo to combo
in with liquidity and everything like
that so generally guys let's dive right
into it sorry for taking so long is we
want to develop this longer longer term
frame higher time frame bias here and we
can see that we are coming back down
here we are uh breaking the structure
over and over onto the downside here so
what i would say is since we are
breaking these levels right here's
there's kind of a low you could also use
the candle body uh whatever you choose
there for your your your um trend um
your trend following guide there right
and so we're going to just use the body
here and we are in kind of a downtrend
on that higher time frame despite having
this very massive move you may say hey
there's a there's an uptrend here and
we're probably going to go up but it is
actually an uptrend on a higher
timeframe so let's jump this one the
daily and you can say okay well
that's that major move so we're in an
uptrend on the daily because we are
breaking these legs right here these
levels right here right
uh we broke that one there and now we're
in the uptrend there kind of swept these
levels but not important so
what's actually happening here is just
because there's a impulsive move doesn't
mean that we're in a uptrend what we're
actually seeing is we're in a downtrend
on this level here so we're going to be
looking for areas that we'd want to get
in on shorts now obviously we're going
to look for untested zones that place
untested meaning places where the levels
have not or the levels have not been
retested after they've broken down so if
you're looking at these higher time
frame here
generally what we can do is we can say
hey
this is a very obvious level right here
right that we broke down from we closed
beyond and then we came back and
retested right here on this candle right
there right so now we're retesting it
again so it's not really interesting to
us anymore
but that is something that we can check
out right so let's look at what that
looked like for an example
so what what happened here right so we
are in the downtrend since we were
broken that and broke again
and now we came back up here and that is
that wick there so once we came back up
here we entered into a
long trend here and what we want to do
is as we're entering back into the zone
we want to say hey let's wait for the
reversal and this is one example of how
this trend trading strategy can be used
i'm using it slightly different way as
well but this video we're just going to
dive in make sure you hit the subscribe
because i will release some more info of
how we might want to be trend trading uh
in the future so all we can do is we can
say um hey look we had the consolidation
here we had the little sweep around
and then we had the reversal so all i'm
telling you guys right now is a reversal
and then there's going to be a re-test
so every single time what we do is we
create consolidation we hunt liquidity
and then we reverse and that's how
things are going to reverse and once
again guys i'm not going to break this
down into massive detail there will be
no strategy i give you guys uh where i'm
going to tell you exactly what i'm doing
uh because that would ruin uh kind of uh
the things i've talked about with other
people um and
uh my own trading method in itself i
don't want things to be fully leaked um
without the permission of people who
have helped me in the past and um
uh because i don't want to ruin it
myself either so we can say hey look
there's this area that after we've
broken out from it we've now switched
our trend to the downside we've come
back to retest it and if you missed this
retest maybe you would have gotten this
one because you would have gotten there
right so now we enter back into that
downtrend and we take this short
entering off the zone
right and then we look to get out
um as it's coming back down to these
levels so if we're looking down here you
can say hey where's an obvious level
well clearly this zone i'm going to just
draw it kind of loosely here somewhere
in that zone is obvious right you could
have looked at this too but then we can
also look at the higher time frame so
what happened on the higher time frame
here well obviously we had a close here
below and we had to close here below
these were the two major candles so
what's probably going to happen is let's
say we just draw one of these hidden
demand zones right there right
and look at that look how well that
lines up with that purple zone we go
right into that purple zone right
on the higher time frame so we're
targeting the higher time frame so we're
using the higher time frame to find our
levels
and then we're using the lower time
frame to enter the trends right and you
can really trade this way guys uh this
is a good way that you're going to make
really accurate trades
maybe we want to check out another
example here let's look at nasdaq really
quick here
let's look here
let's just kind of look again a
downtrend type scenario right so uh we
reversed our trend here we were coming
up we closed some really strong bearish
moves there right
and then we come back to retest
this
sort of
resistance right i drew it in blue this
time i suppose so um let's see how that
works there so let's look
[Music]
just a random chart there right so
we see
that we are in fact if you guys don't
know exactly how we trend trading we
want to check out that video series i
made a long long time ago years back on
how to trade trends uh with price action
so we had a couple moves up here pull
back there and then right there uh is
our peak and then we made a reversal and
you had a couple opportunities to enter
in on this on that reversal after we
touched that blue and what we're gonna
do
is again let's look okay higher time
frame where's the target on the higher
time frame let's draw in purple this
time well we have this hidden demand
here right
i'm just going to draw that out right
there you can see hidden demand and look
where do we target boom we hit it
perfect so 100 win rate right there
super accurate guys
um
good luck that's all i want to say
please
[Music]
uh